<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Guillemets Project</title>
    <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Guillemets Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 03:25:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theguillemetsproject.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> ✨ Ep 2: Google Translate: A World Without Language Barriers?</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/ep2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 03:25:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/ep2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ✨ Ep 1: Our Journey Through French</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/page/</guid>
      <description>Listen to our &amp;ldquo;Journey through French&amp;rdquo; on the following platforms. Available to listen on all podcast platforms Transcription: SS: Ouvrez les guillemets.
AO: Welcome to The Guillemets Project, a UVA podcast about language learning and technology.
AO: Bienvenue au notre premier épisode du podcast, un épisode bilingue en Anglais et en Français.
SS: Bonjour, je m’appelle Spyros, et je suis enseignant de français à l’université de Virginie.
AO: Salut, je m’appelle Alexis, et je suis étudiante d’informatique et de français à l’université de virginie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trailer Episode</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 16:51:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/posts/trailer/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our podcast! Our project explores how real-life online technology impacts French language learning. Join us on our journey!
Available to listen on all podcast platforms Transcription: AO: How does technology impact language learning?
SS: Since when has the internet become a dictionary? How many other digital platforms are frequently used by language students, and what are they?
AO: There are countless language learning applications, but do they really deliver on their promise to make you bilingual?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 21:07:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/podcast/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Guillemets Project (Trailer)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voices</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 11:55:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/voices/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://theguillemetsproject.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 18:46:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theguillemetsproject.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenue! The Guillemets Project is designed by Spyridon Simotas and Alexis Osipovs at the University of Virginia. Our project is exploring how online real-life technology impacts French language learning. One of our primary objectives is to emphasize the importance and benefits of learning French, as well as any other world language, and to engage with students through various creative media. </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
